Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XLVII is arranged in 28 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XLVII. 1925 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 308-0. 1925 Convention
    - Report of the Grand Executive Board -1925 (Box 493, Folder 9-18)
    - Report of the Grand Secretary-Treasurer -1925 (Box 493, Folder 19-23)
    - Proceedings, 1925 (Box 493, Folder 24-38)
    - Report of the National Legislative Counsel, 1925 (Box 493, Folder 39-43)
    - Report of the Grand President, 1925 (Box 493, Folder 44-48)
    - Supplementary Report of the Grand Executive Board on Court Case, 1925 (Box 493, Folder 49-53)
    - Supplementary Report of Vice Grand President Baldwin, H.F. on the Brotherhood Investment Company, 1925 (Box 493, Folder 54-58)
    - Report of the Committee on Legislation, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 1-12)
    - Official Call, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 13-14)
    - Amendments to the Constitution Submitted By Delegates, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 15-21)
    - General, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 22-27)
  - Sub-Series 308-1. 1925 Convention
    - Convention City, 1922 (Box 494, Folder 28)
    - Convention City, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 308-2. 1925 Convention
    - Appeals to the Grand Lodge Convention, 1922 (Box 494, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 308-3. 1925 Convention
    - Committee on Appeals, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 308-4. 1925 Convention
    - Convention Book, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 308-5. 1925 Convention
    - Proposed Amendments to Grand Lodge Laws, 1923 (Box 494, Folder 33)
    - Proposed Amendments to Grand Lodge Laws, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 34)
    - Proposed Amendments to Grand Lodge Laws, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 35-37)
    - Proposed Amendments to Grand Lodge Laws, 1925-1927 (Box 494, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 308-6. 1925 Convention
    - Report of the Grand President, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 39)
    - Report of the Grand President, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 308-7. 1925 Convention
    - Ritual, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 41-42)
  - Sub-Series 308-8. 1925 Convention
    - Convention Hall, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 43)
    - Convention Hall, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 308-9. 1925 Convention
    - Delegates, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 45)
    - Delegates, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 308-10. 1925 Convention
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 47)
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1924-1925 (Box 494, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 308-12. 1925 Convention
    - Vice Grand Presidents' Reports, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 49)
    - Vice Grand Presidents' Reports, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 308-13. 1925 Convention
    - Travel Routes, 1924 (Box 494, Folder 51)
    - Travel Routes, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 308-14. 1925 Convention
    - Grand Lodge Officers, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 308-16. 1925 Convention
    - Pullman Rates, 1925 (Box 494, Folder 54-55)
    - Pullman Rates, 1925-1928 (Box 494, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 308-17. 1925 Convention
    - Resolution No. 19, 1925-1926 (Box 495, Folder 1)
    - Resolution No. 19, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 308-18. 1925 Convention
    - Official Badges, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 308-19. 1925 Convention
    - Arrangements, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 308-20. 1925 Convention
    - Committees. Revised Constitution, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - Committees, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 6)
    - Committees, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 7)
      1925 August
    - Committees, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 8)
      March-April 1925.
  - Sub-Series 308-21. 1925 Convention
    - Transportation Delegates, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 308-22. 1925 Convention
    - Circulars, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 308-23. 1925 Convention
    - Per Diem, 1925-1927 (Box 495, Folder 11)
    - Per Diem, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 308-24. 1925 Convention
    - Advances to Employees, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 308-25. 1925 Convention
    - Visitors Cards, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 308-26. 1925 Convention
    - Appeal of Riley, J.F., 1925 (Box 495, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 308-27. 1925 Convention
    - Proceedings, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 308-28. 1925 Convention
    - Express Caucus, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 308-29. 1925 Convention
    - Special Committee on Representation, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 18)